USER: "John Smith works at ABC Corporation in New York."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"John Smith"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Corporation"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New York"}]

USER: "Please contact Jane Doe at j.doe@email.com for inquiries."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Jane Doe"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"j.doe@email.com"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.com for more information."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.com"}]

USER: "The event will be held on 01/15/2023 at 3:00 PM."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"01/15/2023"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"3:00 PM"}]

USER: "Call our customer support at +1 (555) 123-4567 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+1 (555) 123-4567"}]

USER: "His account number is 1234567890."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"1234567890"}]

USER: "She is 35 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"}]

USER: "Mary Johnson, CEO of XYZ Company, lives at 123 Main Street, Anytown, USA."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mary Johnson"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"CEO"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Company"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Main Street"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Anytown, USA"}]

USER: "The meeting will be held in Conference Room A."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Conference Room A"}]

USER: "David is a software engineer in San Francisco, California."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"David"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"San Francisco, California"}]

USER: "John Smith, an engineer at ABC Company, lives at 123 Main Street, San Francisco, CA."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"John Smith"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Company"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Main Street"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"San Francisco, CA"}]

USER: "Contact us at +1 (555) 123-4567 or support@email.com for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+1 (555) 123-4567"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@email.com"}]

USER: "The event will take place on 2023-09-15 at www.example.com with ID #12345."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"2023-09-15"},{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.com"},{"entity":"ID","text":"12345"}]

USER: "Rajesh Kumar, a software engineer, resides at 56A, Park Street, Kolkata, West Bengal, India. His contact number is +91 9876543210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Kumar"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"56A, Park Street, Kolkata, West Bengal, India"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 9876543210"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"West Bengal"},{"entity":"COUNTRY","text":"India"}]

USER: "Sunita Sharma, born on 15/07/1980, is the CEO of ABC India Pvt. Ltd., headquartered at 123 Corporate Avenue, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. You can reach her at sunita@email.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sunita Sharma"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"15/07/1980"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"CEO"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC India Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Corporate Avenue, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sunita@email.com"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Maharashtra"},{"entity":"COUNTRY","text":"India"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.indiabusiness.com for more information about our services in New Delhi, India. Contact us at info@indiabusiness.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.indiabusiness.com"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@indiabusiness.com"},{"entity":"COUNTRY","text":"India"}]

USER: "Ramesh Kumar, an employee at ABC Technologies Pvt. Ltd., lives at 45/7, Prashant Vihar, New Delhi, India. His email is ramesh.kumar@email.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ramesh Kumar"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Technologies Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"45/7, Prashant Vihar, New Delhi, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"ramesh.kumar@email.in"}]

USER: "Sneha Patel, born on 02/15/1990, is a software engineer at XYZ Software Solutions in Mumbai. Her phone number is +91 (987) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sneha Patel"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"02/15/1990"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.indiaexample.com and contact us at info@indiaexample.com. Our company, India Enterprises Pvt. Ltd., is situated in Pune District."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.indiaexample.com"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@indiaexample.com"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"India Enterprises Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"COUNTY","text":"Pune District"}]

USER: "Priya Sharma, an accountant at Financial Consultants Ltd., resides at 789, Green Park, Kolkata, West Bengal, India. Her contact number is +91 (987) 987-9876."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Priya Sharma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"accountant"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Financial Consultants Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789, Green Park, Kolkata, West Bengal, India"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 987-9876"}]

USER: "The seminar will be held at the Taj Palace Hotel, New Delhi, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Taj Palace Hotel, New Delhi, India"}]

USER: "For banking inquiries, call the State Bank of India at 1800-123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"State Bank of India"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-123-4567"}]

USER: "Our office is located at 56, MG Road, Bangalore, Karnataka, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"56, MG Road, Bangalore, Karnataka, India"}]

USER: "Amit Singh, a marketing manager at XYZ Marketing Services Pvt. Ltd., can be reached at amit.singh@email.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Amit Singh"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"marketing manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Marketing Services Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"amit.singh@email.co.in"}]

USER: "To book a cab, visit www.cabserviceindia.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.cabserviceindia.com"}]

USER: "Deepak Verma, born on 05/10/1982, works as an engineer in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India. His contact number is +91 (987) 765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Deepak Verma"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"05/10/1982"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"engineer"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 765-4321"}]

USER: "For technical support, call XYZ Tech Solutions at +91 (987) 654-9876."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Tech Solutions"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-9876"}]

USER: "We are based in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"}]

USER: "Our company, India Services Ltd., is located at 123, MG Road, New Delhi, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"India Services Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123, MG Road, New Delhi, India"}]

USER: "For inquiries, contact support@indiahelpdesk.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.in"}]

USER: "Rajesh Verma, a professor at ABC University in Pune, can be reached at rajesh.verma@email.edu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Verma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"professor"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC University"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"rajesh.verma@email.edu"}]

USER: "The conference will take place at the India Convention Center, Bengaluru, Karnataka, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"India Convention Center, Bengaluru, Karnataka, India"}]

USER: "For any assistance, please call the India Helpdesk at 24/7 helpline +91 (987) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"India Helpdesk"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 123-4567"}]

USER: "Pay your bills online at www.billpaymentindia.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.billpaymentindia.com"}]

USER: "Nisha Gupta, born on 11/25/1995, is a software developer in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. Her contact number is +91 (987) 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Nisha Gupta"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"11/25/1995"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad, Telangana, India"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 987-6543"}]

USER: "Our company, India Foods Pvt. Ltd., is headquartered at 789, Park Street, Kolkata, West Bengal, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"India Foods Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789, Park Street, Kolkata, West Bengal, India"}]

USER: "Rahul Sharma lives at 45 Park Street, Mumbai, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rahul Sharma"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"45 Park Street, Mumbai, India"}]

USER: "You can contact our support team at support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@example.com"}]

USER: "The event will be held in Hyderabad, Telangana."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad, Telangana"}]

USER: "She is a software engineer at Tech Solutions Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Tech Solutions Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "His age is 30 years."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"30 years"}]

USER: "The company's website is www.techsolutions.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.techsolutions.in"}]

USER: "You can reach me at +91 (123) 456-7890."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (123) 456-7890"}]

USER: "She holds an Aadhaar card with number 1234 5678 9012."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"1234 5678 9012"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.0.1."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.0.1"}]

USER: "He is the CEO of ABC Enterprises."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"ABC Enterprises"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"CEO"}]

USER: "Our office is located at 55 MG Road, Bangalore, Karnataka."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"55 MG Road, Bangalore, Karnataka"}]

USER: "She is a resident of Delhi, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi, India"}]

USER: "The county fair will be in Jaipur, Rajasthan."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Jaipur, Rajasthan"}]

USER: "Her PAN card number is ABCDE1234F."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"ABCDE1234F"}]

USER: "You can visit our website at www.example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.co.in"}]

USER: "Please provide your account number: 9876543210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"9876543210"}]

USER: "The team lead is Mr. Rajesh Kumar."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Kumar"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"team lead"}]

USER: "She is 25 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"25 years"}]

USER: "You can contact the support team at support@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@example.co.in"}]

USER: "The server's IP address is 10.0.0.1."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"10.0.0.1"}]

USER: "Rahul Kumar works at Infosys Technologies Pvt. Ltd. His email is rahul.kumar@infosys.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rahul Kumar"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Infosys Technologies Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"rahul.kumar@infosys.com"}]

USER: "I live in Mumbai, Maharashtra."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, Maharashtra"}]

USER: "Contact the support team at +91 (987) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"}]

USER: "My bank account number is 1234567890123456."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"1234567890123456"}]

USER: "My Aadhaar ID is 1234 5678 9012."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"1234 5678 9012"}]

USER: "Email me at user123@gmail.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"user123@gmail.com"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in"}]

USER: "I am 25 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"25 years old"}]

USER: "I work for TATA Consultancy Services as a software engineer."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"TATA Consultancy Services"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"}]

USER: "My gender is female."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"}]

USER: "I live at 456 Park Street, Bangalore."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 Park Street, Bangalore"}]

USER: "I'm from Pune, Maharashtra."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune, Maharashtra"}]

USER: "Contact the IT department at +91 (876) 543-2109."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 543-2109"}]

USER: "My bank account number is 9876543210987654."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"9876543210987654"}]

USER: "My PAN card ID is ABCDE1234F."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"ABCDE1234F"}]

USER: "Email me at contact.me@domain.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact.me@domain.co.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.co.in"}]

USER: "I am 30 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"30 years old"}]

USER: "I work for Wipro as a project manager."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Wipro"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"}]

USER: "My gender is male."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"}]

USER: "I live at 789 Green Road, Delhi."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Green Road, Delhi"}]

USER: "I'm from Kolkata, West Bengal."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata, West Bengal"}]

USER: "Contact the customer service at +91 (765) 432-1098."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (765) 432-1098"}]

USER: "My bank account number is 8765432109876543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"8765432109876543"}]

USER: "My Voter ID is XYZ1234567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"XYZ1234567"}]

USER: "Email me at support@domain.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@domain.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.net.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.net.in"}]

USER: "I am 40 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"40 years old"}]

USER: "I work for HCL Technologies as a data analyst."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"HCL Technologies"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"data analyst"}]

USER: "My gender is other."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"other"}]

USER: "I live at 123 Blue Street, Chennai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Blue Street, Chennai"}]

USER: "I'm from Hyderabad, Telangana."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad, Telangana"}]

USER: "Contact the HR department at +91 (987) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"}]

USER: "My bank account number is 7654321098765432."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"7654321098765432"}]

USER: "My Passport ID is P1234567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"P1234567"}]

USER: "Email me at info@website.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@website.co.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.org.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.org.in"}]

USER: "I am 50 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"50 years old"}]

USER: "I work for Tech Mahindra as a software developer."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Tech Mahindra"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"}]

USER: "My gender is prefer not to say."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"prefer not to say"}]

USER: "I live at 567 Red Road, Pune."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"567 Red Road, Pune"}]

USER: "I'm from Jaipur, Rajasthan."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Jaipur, Rajasthan"}]

USER: "Contact the billing department at +91 (876) 543-2109."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 543-2109"}]

USER: "My bank account number is 6543210987654321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"6543210987654321"}]

USER: "My Driving License ID is DL1234567890."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"DL1234567890"}]

USER: "Email me at contactus@domain.org.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contactus@domain.org.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.co.org.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.co.org.in"}]

USER: "I am 60 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"60 years old"}]

USER: "I work for Reliance Industries as a manager."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Reliance Industries"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"manager"}]

USER: "My gender is unknown."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"unknown"}]

USER: "I spoke with Raj Sharma from Mumbai, his phone number is 9876543210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Raj Sharma"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"9876543210"}]

USER: "My PAN card number is ABCDE1234F."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"ABCDE1234F"}]

USER: "Send an email to priya@email.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"priya@email.com"}]

USER: "Check out the website at www.example.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in"}]

USER: "Amit is a 35-year-old engineer at ABC Ltd. in New Delhi."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Amit"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35-year-old"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi"}]

USER: "Sheela lives at 123, Park Street, Kolkata."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sheela"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123, Park Street, Kolkata"}]

USER: "The office is in Mumbai, Maharashtra."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, Maharashtra"}]

USER: "Call support at +91 98765 43210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 98765 43210"}]

USER: "I'm working at XYZ Solutions Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Solutions Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Visit the official government site at www.india.gov.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.india.gov.in"}]

USER: "My employee ID is EMP12345."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"EMP12345"}]

USER: "Rahul is the manager."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rahul"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"manager"}]

USER: "I live at 456, MG Road, Bengaluru, Karnataka."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456, MG Road, Bengaluru, Karnataka"}]

USER: "The company headquarters is in Hyderabad, Telangana."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad, Telangana"}]

USER: "I am 28 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"28 years old"}]

USER: "Please send an email to contact@company.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@company.co.in"}]

USER: "The IP address is 192.168.1.1."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.1.1"}]

USER: "My bank account number is 1234567890."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"1234567890"}]

USER: "She is from Chennai, Tamil Nadu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai, Tamil Nadu"}]

USER: "The county fair is in Pune, Maharashtra."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COUNTY","text":"Pune, Maharashtra"}]

USER: "I would like to contact Mr. Rajesh Sharma at rajesh@email.com for a job opportunity."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Sharma"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"rajesh@email.com"}]

USER: "My phone number is +91 (123) 456-7890 and my account number is IN123456789."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (123) 456-7890"},{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN123456789"}]

USER: "The conference will be held at Mumbai, Maharashtra, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"}]

USER: "I live at 456 Park Street, Bengaluru, Karnataka, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 Park Street, Bengaluru, Karnataka, India"}]

USER: "Please visit our website at www.example.in for more information."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in"}]

USER: "She is a software engineer at XYZ Solutions, Bangalore, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"She"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore, India"}]

USER: "My age is 30 years."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"30 years"}]

USER: "The company, ABC Enterprises, is located in New Delhi, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Enterprises"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi, India"}]

USER: "I have an ID card with the number IND987654."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND987654"}]

USER: "The IP address of our server is 192.168.1.100."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.1.100"}]

USER: "Ramesh Kumar, an engineer at ABC Pvt. Ltd., lives at 456 Green Park, New Delhi, India. His email is ramesh@email.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ramesh Kumar"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 Green Park, New Delhi, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"ramesh@email.co.in"}]

USER: "The event will be held at the Taj Mahal Hotel, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. Contact us at events@tajmahalhotel.in for more information."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Taj Mahal Hotel, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"events@tajmahalhotel.in"}]

USER: "To book a cab, call +91 (987) 654-3210. We operate in Bangalore, Karnataka, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore, Karnataka, India"}]

USER: "My Aadhaar number is 1234 5678 9876."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"1234 5678 9876"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.in for more details."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in"}]

USER: "She is 30 years old and works as a software developer in Hyderabad, Telangana, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"30 years old"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad, Telangana, India"}]

USER: "XYZ Ltd., headquartered in Pune, Maharashtra, India, is a leading IT company."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune, Maharashtra, India"}]

USER: "Mr. Rajesh Sharma, an architect, resides at 789 Silver Lane, Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mr. Rajesh Sharma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"architect"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Silver Lane, Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India"}]

USER: "The meeting will take place at 101 Park Street, Kolkata, West Bengal, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"101 Park Street, Kolkata, West Bengal, India"}]

USER: "For support, contact us at support@yourcompany.co.in. Our office is located at 123 Tech Park, Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@yourcompany.co.in"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Tech Park, Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India"}]

USER: "Sheela Verma, a teacher, is 45 years old and lives at 567 Hillside Road, Jaipur, Rajasthan, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sheela Verma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"teacher"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"45 years old"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"567 Hillside Road, Jaipur, Rajasthan, India"}]

USER: "Please call +91 (987) 123-4567 for assistance. Our office is in Gurgaon, Haryana, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 123-4567"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Gurgaon, Haryana, India"}]

USER: "My PAN card number is ABCDE1234F."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"ABCDE1234F"}]

USER: "Check out our website at www.indiaexample.com for more information."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.indiaexample.com"}]

USER: "He is 28 years old and works as a marketing manager in Pune, Maharashtra, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"28 years old"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"marketing manager"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune, Maharashtra, India"}]

USER: "ABC Electronics Pvt. Ltd., with its office in Delhi, India, is a renowned electronics manufacturer."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Electronics Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi, India"}]

USER: "Mr. Sunil Gupta, a lawyer, resides at 456 Lakeview Apartments, Bangalore, Karnataka, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mr. Sunil Gupta"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"lawyer"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 Lakeview Apartments, Bangalore, Karnataka, India"}]

USER: "The seminar will be held at 789 Convention Center, Hyderabad, Telangana, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Convention Center, Hyderabad, Telangana, India"}]

USER: "For inquiries, email us at info@yourcompany.in. Our office is situated at 101 Tech Hub, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@yourcompany.in"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"101 Tech Hub, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"}]

USER: "Connect to the network with IP address 192.168.1.100 in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.1.100"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India"}]

USER: "Rahul Gupta, a 40-year-old male, resides at 123 Green Park, New Delhi. His phone number is +91 (987) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rahul Gupta"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"40 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Green Park, New Delhi"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"}]

USER: "Visit our company's website at www.example.co.in. Contact us at contact@example.co.in. Our office is located at 456 Business Tower, Mumbai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.co.in"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@example.co.in"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 Business Tower, Mumbai"}]

USER: "The event will be held on 06/25/2023 at Bangalore International Exhibition Center, Bengaluru."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"06/25/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore International Exhibition Center, Bengaluru"}]

USER: "Sneha Verma, a 28-year-old female, is the CEO of ABC India Pvt. Ltd. She lives at 789 Serene Lane, Chennai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sneha Verma"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"28 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"CEO"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC India Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Serene Lane, Chennai"}]

USER: "For support, contact our helpline at 1800-123-4567 or email support@help.co.in. Our headquarters are in Mumbai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-123-4567"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@help.co.in"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"}]

USER: "The unique ID for this transaction is IN567823. Please contact our India office at india.office@example.com for more information."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IN567823"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.office@example.com"}]

USER: "Amit Kumar, aged 32, is a software engineer at XYZ Tech Solutions, Hyderabad. You can reach him at +91 (789) 456-1234."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Amit Kumar"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"32"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Tech Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 456-1234"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 203.0.113.12, and it's hosted by Hosting India Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"203.0.113.12"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is located at 567 Business Park, New Delhi. Contact us at india@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"567 Business Park, New Delhi"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india@example.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the account number for your INR savings account: IN1234567890."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN1234567890"}]

USER: "Rajesh Sharma, a 45-year-old male, is the HR Manager at ABC India Pvt. Ltd. He is based in Kolkata."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Sharma"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"45 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"HR Manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC India Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata"}]

USER: "The training session is scheduled for 09/10/2023 at the Mumbai Training Center."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"09/10/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai Training Center"}]

USER: "Contact our customer support at +91 (876) 543-2109 or email us at support@indiasupport.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 543-2109"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiasupport.co.in"}]

USER: "The conference will take place in New Delhi on 12/05/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"12/05/2023"}]

USER: "Our office is at 123 Corporate Avenue, Bangalore. Contact us at info@companyindia.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Corporate Avenue, Bangalore"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@companyindia.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the transaction ID: IND567890. For queries, contact india.support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND567890"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.support@example.com"}]

USER: "Sheela Mehta, a 35-year-old female, works as a project manager at XYZ Solutions, Mumbai. Her contact number is +91 (987) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sheela Mehta"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"}]

USER: "For support, dial our helpline at 1800-789-1234 or email support@indiahelpdesk.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-789-1234"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.co.in"}]

USER: "The event venue is Jaipur Exhibition Hall, Jaipur, on 11/15/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Jaipur Exhibition Hall, Jaipur"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/15/2023"}]

USER: "Avinash Patel, aged 29, is a software developer at ABC Software Solutions, Pune. You can reach him at +91 (789) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Avinash Patel"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"29"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-4567"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.1.10, and it's hosted by Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.1.10"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is at 789 Business Plaza, Mumbai. Contact us at india.contact@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Business Plaza, Mumbai"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.contact@example.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the account number for your INR current account: IN2345678901."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN2345678901"}]

USER: "Manisha Singh, a 42-year-old female, is the Marketing Manager at XYZ Marketing Solutions, Hyderabad. She is based in Hyderabad."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Manisha Singh"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"42 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"Marketing Manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Marketing Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad"}]

USER: "The training session is scheduled for 10/15/2023 at the Kolkata Training Center."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"10/15/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata Training Center"}]

USER: "Contact our customer support at +91 (876) 987-6543 or email us at support@indiasupport.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiasupport.co.in"}]

USER: "The conference will take place in Delhi on 12/12/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"12/12/2023"}]

USER: "Our office is at 456 Tech Park, Pune. Contact us at info@companyindia.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 Tech Park, Pune"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@companyindia.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the transaction ID: IND678901. For queries, contact india.support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND678901"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.support@example.com"}]

USER: "Rajeev Malhotra, a 39-year-old male, works as a project manager at XYZ Projects, Bangalore. His contact number is +91 (789) 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajeev Malhotra"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"39 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Projects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 987-6543"}]

USER: "For support, dial our helpline at 1800-987-6543 or email support@indiahelpdesk.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.co.in"}]

USER: "The event venue is Hyderabad Convention Center, Hyderabad, on 11/20/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad Convention Center, Hyderabad"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/20/2023"}]

USER: "Anjali Desai, aged 31, is a software developer at ABC Software Solutions, Mumbai. You can reach her at +91 (789) 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Anjali Desai"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"31"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 987-6543"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.0.1, and it's hosted by Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.0.1"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is at 890 Business Park, Chennai. Contact us at india.contact@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"890 Business Park, Chennai"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.contact@example.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the account number for your INR savings account: IN3456789012."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN3456789012"}]

USER: "Smita Reddy, a 35-year-old female, is the HR Manager at XYZ India Pvt. Ltd. She is based in Chennai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Smita Reddy"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"HR Manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ India Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai"}]

USER: "The training session is scheduled for 11/05/2023 at the Mumbai Training Center."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/05/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai Training Center"}]

USER: "Contact our customer support at +91 (876) 654-3210 or email us at support@indiasupport.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 654-3210"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiasupport.co.in"}]

USER: "The conference will take place in Bangalore on 12/18/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"12/18/2023"}]

USER: "Our office is at 567 Tech Park, Hyderabad. Contact us at info@companyindia.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"567 Tech Park, Hyderabad"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@companyindia.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the transaction ID: IND789012. For queries, contact india.support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND789012"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.support@example.com"}]

USER: "Nikhil Gupta, a 34-year-old male, works as a project manager at XYZ Projects, Pune. His contact number is +91 (789) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Nikhil Gupta"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"34 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Projects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 654-3210"}]

USER: "For support, dial our helpline at 1800-654-3210 or email support@indiahelpdesk.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-654-3210"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.co.in"}]

USER: "The event venue is Delhi Convention Center, Delhi, on 11/25/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi Convention Center, Delhi"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/25/2023"}]

USER: "Alok Sharma, aged 32, is a software developer at ABC Software Solutions, Bangalore. You can reach him at +91 (789) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Alok Sharma"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"32"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-4567"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.2.1, and it's hosted by Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.2.1"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is at 678 Business Plaza, Kolkata. Contact us at india.contact@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"678 Business Plaza, Kolkata"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.contact@example.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the account number for your INR current account: IN4567890123."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN4567890123"}]

USER: "Snehal Deshmukh, a 37-year-old female, is the Marketing Manager at XYZ Marketing Solutions, Chennai. She is based in Chennai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Snehal Deshmukh"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"37 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"Marketing Manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Marketing Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai"}]

USER: "The training session is scheduled for 10/30/2023 at the Hyderabad Training Center."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"10/30/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad Training Center"}]

USER: "Contact our customer support at +91 (876) 987-6543 or email us at support@indiasupport.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiasupport.co.in"}]

USER: "The conference will take place in Mumbai on 12/30/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"12/30/2023"}]

USER: "Our office is at 678 Tech Park, Kolkata. Contact us at info@companyindia.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"678 Tech Park, Kolkata"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@companyindia.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the transaction ID: IND890123. For queries, contact india.support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND890123"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.support@example.com"}]

USER: "Neha Joshi, a 36-year-old female, works as a project manager at XYZ Projects, Chennai. Her contact number is +91 (789) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Neha Joshi"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"36 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Projects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 654-3210"}]

USER: "For support, dial our helpline at 1800-987-6543 or email support@indiahelpdesk.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.co.in"}]

USER: "The event venue is Bangalore Convention Center, Bangalore, on 11/30/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore Convention Center, Bangalore"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/30/2023"}]

USER: "Vishal Mishra, aged 33, is a software developer at ABC Software Solutions, Delhi. You can reach him at +91 (789) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Vishal Mishra"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"33"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-4567"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.3.1, and it's hosted by Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.3.1"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is at 789 Business Plaza, Chennai. Contact us at india.contact@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Business Plaza, Chennai"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.contact@example.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the account number for your INR savings account: IN5678901234."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN5678901234"}]

USER: "Sarita Rajan, a 38-year-old female, is the HR Manager at XYZ India Pvt. Ltd. She is based in Mumbai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sarita Rajan"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"38 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"HR Manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ India Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"}]

USER: "The training session is scheduled for 10/20/2023 at the Delhi Training Center."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"10/20/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi Training Center"}]

USER: "Contact our customer support at +91 (876) 987-6543 or email us at support@indiasupport.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiasupport.co.in"}]

USER: "The conference will take place in Chennai on 12/12/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"12/12/2023"}]

USER: "Our office is at 890 Tech Park, Kolkata. Contact us at info@companyindia.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"890 Tech Park, Kolkata"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@companyindia.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the transaction ID: IND901234. For queries, contact india.support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND901234"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.support@example.com"}]

USER: "Kunal Shah, a 41-year-old male, works as a project manager at XYZ Projects, Hyderabad. His contact number is +91 (789) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Kunal Shah"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"41 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Projects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 654-3210"}]

USER: "For support, dial our helpline at 1800-987-6543 or email support@indiahelpdesk.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.co.in"}]

USER: "The event venue is Mumbai Convention Center, Mumbai, on 11/10/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai Convention Center, Mumbai"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/10/2023"}]

USER: "Akash Mehra, aged 30, is a software developer at ABC Software Solutions, Kolkata. You can reach him at +91 (789) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Akash Mehra"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"30"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-4567"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.4.1, and it's hosted by Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.4.1"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is at 567 Business Plaza, Hyderabad. Contact us at india.contact@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"567 Business Plaza, Hyderabad"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.contact@example.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the account number for your INR current account: IN6789012345."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN6789012345"}]

USER: "Aarav Mehta, a 37-year-old male, is the Marketing Manager at XYZ Marketing Solutions, Delhi. He is based in Delhi."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Aarav Mehta"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"37 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"Marketing Manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Marketing Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"}]

USER: "The training session is scheduled for 10/10/2023 at the Chennai Training Center."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"10/10/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai Training Center"}]

USER: "Contact our customer support at +91 (876) 987-6543 or email us at support@indiasupport.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiasupport.co.in"}]

USER: "The conference will take place in Kolkata on 12/05/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"12/05/2023"}]

USER: "Our office is at 789 Tech Park, Hyderabad. Contact us at info@companyindia.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Tech Park, Hyderabad"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@companyindia.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the transaction ID: IND012345. For queries, contact india.support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND012345"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.support@example.com"}]

USER: "Amita Kapoor, a 32-year-old female, works as a project manager at XYZ Projects, Chennai. Her contact number is +91 (789) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Amita Kapoor"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"32 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Projects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 654-3210"}]

USER: "For support, dial our helpline at 1800-987-6543 or email support@indiahelpdesk.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.co.in"}]

USER: "The event venue is Delhi Convention Center, Delhi, on 11/15/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi Convention Center, Delhi"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/15/2023"}]

USER: "Sanjay Verma, aged 29, is a software developer at ABC Software Solutions, Hyderabad. You can reach him at +91 (789) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sanjay Verma"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"29"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-4567"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.5.1, and it's hosted by Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.5.1"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is at 456 Business Plaza, Chennai. Contact us at india.contact@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 Business Plaza, Chennai"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.contact@example.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the account number for your INR savings account: IN7890123456."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"IN7890123456"}]

USER: "Preeti Desai, a 35-year-old female, is the HR Manager at XYZ India Pvt. Ltd. She is based in Kolkata."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Preeti Desai"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"HR Manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ India Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata"}]

USER: "The training session is scheduled for 10/25/2023 at the Mumbai Training Center."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"10/25/2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai Training Center"}]

USER: "Contact our customer support at +91 (876) 987-6543 or email us at support@indiasupport.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (876) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiasupport.co.in"}]

USER: "The conference will take place in Hyderabad on 12/25/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"12/25/2023"}]

USER: "Our office is at 567 Tech Park, Kolkata. Contact us at info@companyindia.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"567 Tech Park, Kolkata"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@companyindia.co.in"}]

USER: "This is the transaction ID: IND123456. For queries, contact india.support@example.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"IND123456"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.support@example.com"}]

USER: "Vikram Kapoor, a 36-year-old male, works as a project manager at XYZ Projects, Delhi. His contact number is +91 (789) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Vikram Kapoor"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"36 years old"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"male"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Projects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 654-3210"}]

USER: "For support, dial our helpline at 1800-987-6543 or email support@indiahelpdesk.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@indiahelpdesk.co.in"}]

USER: "The event venue is Kolkata Convention Center, Kolkata, on 11/05/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata Convention Center, Kolkata"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"11/05/2023"}]

USER: "Rohit Sharma, aged 31, is a software developer at ABC Software Solutions, Chennai. You can reach him at +91 (789) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rohit Sharma"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"31"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Software Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-4567"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.6.1, and it's hosted by Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.6.1"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Hosting India Pvt. Ltd."}]

USER: "Our Indian branch is at 678 Business Plaza, Pune. Contact us at india.contact@example.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"678 Business Plaza, Pune"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"india.contact@example.co.in"}]

USER: "In India, many people have Aadhaar IDs which are 12-digit unique identification numbers. For example, my Aadhaar ID is 1234-5678-9012. I work for XYZ Technologies, a software company located in Bangalore. My email address is john.doe@email.com, and I'm 35 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"India"},{"entity":"ID","text":"1234-5678-9012"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Technologies"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"john.doe@email.com"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"}]

USER: "Mumbai is the capital city of Maharashtra, and it's known for its vibrant culture. The contact number for the local government office is +91 (22) 1234-5678. The website for official information is www.maharashtra.gov.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Maharashtra"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (22) 1234-5678"},{"entity":"URL","text":"www.maharashtra.gov.in"}]

USER: "Ramesh Sharma lives in New Delhi, India. He is a software engineer at ABC Solutions. His employee ID is EMP12345. You can reach him at ramesh.sharma@email.com or +91 (11) 9876-5432."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ramesh Sharma"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi, India"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Solutions"},{"entity":"ID","text":"EMP12345"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"ramesh.sharma@email.com"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (11) 9876-5432"}]

USER: "Bangalore is a major IT hub in India, and it's home to several tech giants like Infosys, Wipro, and TCS. The average age of software engineers in the city is around 30 years."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Infosys"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Wipro"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"TCS"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"30 years"}]

USER: "The government office in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, is responsible for issuing unique ID cards to residents. These cards are essential for accessing various services. My ID card number is CHN-5678-1234."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai, Tamil Nadu"},{"entity":"ID","text":"CHN-5678-1234"}]

USER: "In Hyderabad, many IT professionals work for global companies. The contact number for IT support is +91 (40) 8765-4321. The official website for the city is www.hyderabad.telangana.gov.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (40) 8765-4321"},{"entity":"URL","text":"www.hyderabad.telangana.gov.in"}]

USER: "I am a 45-year-old software engineer working for DEF Tech in Pune. My employee ID is DEF56789. You can contact me at john.smith@email.com or +91 (20) 1234-5678."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"45 years old"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"DEF Tech"},{"entity":"ID","text":"DEF56789"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"john.smith@email.com"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (20) 1234-5678"}]

USER: "Kolkata, also known as Calcutta, is the capital of West Bengal. It's famous for its cultural heritage. The contact number for the local museum is +91 (33) 9876-5432. You can visit their website at www.kolkatamuseum.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kolkata"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Calcutta"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"West Bengal"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (33) 9876-5432"},{"entity":"URL","text":"www.kolkatamuseum.in"}]

USER: "I work at GHI Solutions, a software company based in Noida, Uttar Pradesh. My employee ID is GHI67890. You can reach me at sarah.jones@email.com or +91 (120) 7654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"GHI Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Noida, Uttar Pradesh"},{"entity":"ID","text":"GHI67890"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sarah.jones@email.com"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (120) 7654-3210"}]

USER: "Ahmedabad is a thriving city in Gujarat, known for its business opportunities. The contact number for the local chamber of commerce is +91 (79) 6543-2109. The official website for the city is www.ahmedabad.gov.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Ahmedabad"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Gujarat"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (79) 6543-2109"},{"entity":"URL","text":"www.ahmedabad.gov.in"}]

USER: "Sarika Gupta, an employee at XYZ Technologies, lives at 45 Sunshine Avenue, Bangalore, India. She was born on 15/07/1980 and can be reached at +91 98765 43210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sarika Gupta"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Technologies"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"45 Sunshine Avenue, Bangalore, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"15/07/1980"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 98765 43210"}]

USER: "The annual meeting of ABC Corporation will take place at Hotel Grand View, Mumbai, India. The event is scheduled for 25th September 2023, from 9:00 AM to 5:00 PM."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Corporation"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hotel Grand View, Mumbai, India"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"25th September 2023"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"9:00 AM to 5:00 PM"}]

USER: "Rajat Sharma is an engineer at TechWiz Solutions in Hyderabad, India. His employee ID is TW12345, and his email is rajat@email.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajat Sharma"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"TechWiz Solutions"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad, India"},{"entity":"ID","text":"TW12345"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"rajat@email.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.in for more information about our services. Contact us at contact@example.in for inquiries."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@example.in"}]

USER: "The average age of employees at XYZ Corporation is 35 years. There are 250 employees in the Bangalore office."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Corporation"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore office"}]

USER: "Dr. Ananya Reddy, a renowned cardiologist, practices at Apollo Hospital in Chennai, India. You can book an appointment by calling +91 98765 54321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Dr. Ananya Reddy"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"cardiologist"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Apollo Hospital"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai, India"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 98765 54321"}]

USER: "The manufacturing unit of XYZ Industries is located at 12 Industrial Road, Pune, India. It employs over 500 workers."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Industries"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"12 Industrial Road, Pune, India"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"over 500"}]

USER: "In Mumbai, there are 7,000 confirmed cases of COVID-19 as of 10th August 2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"7,000"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"10th August 2023"}]

USER: "The IP address of the server is 192.168.1.1, and it's hosted in Delhi, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.1.1"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi, India"}]

USER: "We have branches in Delhi, Mumbai, and Bangalore, serving customers all over India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"India"}]

USER: "The company's headquarters is in Hyderabad, and it has a branch office in Jaipur, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Jaipur, India"}]

USER: "Ms. Priya Verma is the HR manager at Global Solutions Pvt. Ltd. Her contact email is priya@globalsolutions.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ms. Priya Verma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"HR manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Global Solutions Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"priya@globalsolutions.in"}]

USER: "The employee with ID E98765 has been with the company for 10 years and works in the Delhi office."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"E98765"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"10 years"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi office"}]

USER: "Please fill out the form at www.example.in/contact-us for inquiries or email us at info@example.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in/contact-us"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@example.in"}]

USER: "The company picnic will be held at Ooty, Tamil Nadu, on 5th October 2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Ooty, Tamil Nadu"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"5th October 2023"}]

USER: "The age limit for the contest is 18 to 35 years. Participants must be residents of India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"18 to 35 years"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"India"}]

USER: "The software development team at TechWorld Innovations comprises 15 engineers and 5 data analysts."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"TechWorld Innovations"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"15 engineers"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"5 data analysts"}]

USER: "The address for returns is 123 Returns Lane, Kolkata, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Returns Lane, Kolkata, India"}]

USER: "All employees must complete their training by 31st December 2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"31st December 2023"}]

USER: "The contact number for customer support is +91 80000 12345. Our support team is available from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM, Monday to Friday."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 80000 12345"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"9:00 AM to 6:00 PM"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"Monday to Friday"}]

USER: "There are 10 branches of XYZ Bank in Mumbai and 5 in Bangalore."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Bank"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"10 branches"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"5"}]

USER: "The current CEO of ABC Corporation is Mr. Rajesh Sharma. The company is headquartered in Delhi."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mr. Rajesh Sharma"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Corporation"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"}]

USER: "The package includes a laptop, a smartphone, and a one-year subscription to our software."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PRODUCT","text":"laptop"},{"entity":"PRODUCT","text":"smartphone"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"one-year subscription"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"our software"}]

USER: "The gender ratio in the IT department is 70% male and 30% female."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"70% male"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"30% female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"IT department"}]

USER: "The company's URL is www.globaltech.in, and their email is contact@globaltech.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.globaltech.in"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@globaltech.in"}]

USER: "The event took place at the Radisson Hotel, Chennai. It was attended by 500 participants."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Radisson Hotel, Chennai"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"500 participants"}]

USER: "All employees are required to complete the mandatory cybersecurity training by 15th November 2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"15th November 2023"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"cybersecurity training"}]

USER: "The company's main office is located at 123 Corporate Avenue, Mumbai, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Corporate Avenue, Mumbai, India"}]

USER: "The phone number for technical support is +91 98765 67890, and it's available 24/7."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 98765 67890"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"24/7"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"technical support"}]

USER: "The company's website is www.techworld.com, and you can reach them at info@techworld.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.techworld.com"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@techworld.com"}]

USER: "The employee's ID card number is EMP123456, and they work in the Delhi office."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"EMP123456"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi office"}]

USER: "The meeting will be held at 10:00 AM on 2nd September 2023 at our Gurgaon office."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"10:00 AM"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"2nd September 2023"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Gurgaon office"}]

USER: "The company's policy states that all employees must wear their ID badges at all times."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"company's policy"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"employees"},{"entity":"ID","text":"ID badges"}]

USER: "The gender distribution in the marketing department is 45% male and 55% female."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"45% male"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"55% female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"marketing department"}]

USER: "The company's head office is in Bangalore, and they have regional offices in Mumbai and Delhi."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"head office"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"regional offices"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"}]

USER: "The employee's date of birth is 05/12/1990, and they are based in Chennai."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"05/12/1990"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai"}]

USER: "The company's website is www.globaltech.in, and their contact email is contact@globaltech.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.globaltech.in"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@globaltech.in"}]

USER: "All employees are required to complete their annual ethics training by 31st December."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"31st December"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"annual ethics training"}]

USER: "The customer helpline number is +91 80000 54321, and it's available from 8:00 AM to 8:00 PM, seven days a week."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 80000 54321"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"8:00 AM to 8:00 PM"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"seven days a week"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"customer helpline"}]

USER: "The company picnic will be held at Ooty, Tamil Nadu, on 5th October 2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Ooty, Tamil Nadu"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"5th October 2023"}]

USER: "The age limit for the contest is 18 to 35 years. Participants must be residents of India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"18 to 35 years"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"residents of India"}]

USER: "The software development team at TechWorld Innovations comprises 15 engineers and 5 data analysts."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"TechWorld Innovations"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"15 engineers"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"5 data analysts"}]

USER: "The company's URL is www.globaltech.in, and their email is contact@globaltech.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.globaltech.in"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@globaltech.in"}]

USER: "The event took place at the Radisson Hotel, Chennai. It was attended by 500 participants."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Radisson Hotel, Chennai"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"500 participants"}]

USER: "All employees must complete their training by 31st December 2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"TIME","text":"31st December 2023"}]

USER: "The contact number for customer support is +91 80000 12345. Our support team is available from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM, Monday to Friday."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 80000 12345"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"9:00 AM to 6:00 PM"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"Monday to Friday"}]

USER: "There are 10 branches of XYZ Bank in Mumbai and 5 in Bangalore."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Bank"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bangalore"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"10 branches"},{"entity":"NUMBER","text":"5"}]

USER: "The current CEO of ABC Corporation is Mr. Rajesh Sharma. The company is headquartered in Delhi."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mr. Rajesh Sharma"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Corporation"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Delhi"}]

USER: "The package includes a laptop, a smartphone, and a one-year subscription to our software."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PRODUCT","text":"laptop"},{"entity":"PRODUCT","text":"smartphone"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"one-year subscription"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"our software"}]

USER: "The gender ratio in the IT department is 70% male and 30% female."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"GENDER","text":"70% male"},{"entity":"GENDER","text":"30% female"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"IT department"}]

USER: "Ramesh Kumar, an employee at ABC Corp, lives at 45 Banerjee Road, Kolkata. His email is ramesh@email.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ramesh Kumar"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Corp"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"45 Banerjee Road, Kolkata"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"ramesh@email.com"}]

USER: "The annual meeting of XYZ Ltd is scheduled at The Taj Hotel, Mumbai on 05/15/2023."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Ltd"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"The Taj Hotel, Mumbai"},{"entity":"TIME","text":"05/15/2023"}]

USER: "Contact our support team at +91 (123) 456-7890 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (123) 456-7890"}]

USER: "Your unique account number is 7890-456-123."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"7890-456-123"}]

USER: "Please provide your Aadhar ID for verification."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"Aadhar ID"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.in for more information."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in"}]

USER: "She is 35 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"}]

USER: "Rajesh Singh is the CEO of Infosys India Pvt Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Singh"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"CEO"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Infosys India Pvt Ltd"}]

USER: "Call our customer support at 1800-123-4567 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"1800-123-4567"}]

USER: "Please send your PAN card to verify your identity."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"PAN card"}]

USER: "For job opportunities at TCS, visit careers.tcs.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"TCS"},{"entity":"URL","text":"careers.tcs.com"}]

USER: "He was born on 01/20/1990."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"01/20/1990"}]

USER: "The headquarters of Reliance Industries is in Mumbai, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Reliance Industries"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, India"}]

USER: "Mr. Sharma is a software engineer at Wipro Technologies."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mr. Sharma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Wipro Technologies"}]

USER: "Contact our HR department at hr@example.co.in for job inquiries."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"hr@example.co.in"}]

USER: "Our office is located at 123 Park Street, Bangalore, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Park Street, Bangalore, India"}]

USER: "The event will be held in Conference Room A."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Conference Room A"}]

USER: "Please contact support@xyz.in for technical issues."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@xyz.in"}]

USER: "Her voter ID number is XYZ1234567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"voter ID number"}]

USER: "The manufacturing plant is located in Gujarat, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Gujarat, India"}]

USER: "For more information, visit our website: www.indiaexample.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.indiaexample.com"}]

USER: "She is 40 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"40 years old"}]

USER: "Rajiv is a manager at Tata Steel Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajiv"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Tata Steel Ltd"}]

USER: "Call our customer service at 0800-987-6543 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"0800-987-6543"}]

USER: "Your passport number is ABC123456."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"passport number"}]

USER: "Visit our careers page at careers.example.in for job openings."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"careers.example.in"}]

USER: "He was born on 02/15/1985."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"02/15/1985"}]

USER: "The headquarters of ONGC is in Dehradun, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ONGC"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Dehradun, India"}]

USER: "Mr. Gupta is a senior engineer at Tech Solutions."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mr. Gupta"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"senior engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Tech Solutions"}]

USER: "Contact our sales team at sales@example.co.in for inquiries."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sales@example.co.in"}]

USER: "Our office is located at 456 IT Park, Hyderabad, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"456 IT Park, Hyderabad, India"}]

USER: "The meeting will be held in Boardroom B."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Boardroom B"}]

USER: "Please contact support@abc.in for assistance with your account."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@abc.in"}]

USER: "His driver's license number is DL-1234567890."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"driver's license number"}]

USER: "The research center is located in Pune, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune, India"}]

USER: "For more information, visit our website: www.indiainfo.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.indiainfo.com"}]

USER: "She is 28 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"28 years old"}]

USER: "Amit is a project manager at Infosys."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Amit"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Infosys"}]

USER: "Call our support hotline at 0800-555-1234 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"0800-555-1234"}]

USER: "Your Aadhar card number is 9876-5432-1234."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"Aadhar card number"}]

USER: "Visit our careers page at careers.tcs.in for job opportunities."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"careers.tcs.in"}]

USER: "He was born on 06/10/1992."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"AGE","text":"06/10/1992"}]

USER: "The headquarters of BHEL is in New Delhi, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"BHEL"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi, India"}]

USER: "Ms. Verma is a senior consultant at Tech Solutions Pvt Ltd."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ms. Verma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"senior consultant"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Tech Solutions Pvt Ltd"}]

USER: "Contact our support team at support@example.co.in for inquiries."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@example.co.in"}]

USER: "Our office is located at 789 Business Park, Chennai, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 Business Park, Chennai, India"}]

USER: "The seminar will be held in Hall C."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hall C"}]

USER: "Please contact help@xyz.in for technical support."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"help@xyz.in"}]

USER: "His passport number is P12345678."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ID","text":"passport number"}]

USER: "The manufacturing facility is located in Pune, India."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune, India"}]

USER: "Ramesh Kumar, an employee at Infosys Technologies Ltd., resides at 45 Gandhi Road, Bengaluru, Karnataka, India. His email is ramesh.kumar@infosys.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ramesh Kumar"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"Infosys Technologies Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"45 Gandhi Road, Bengaluru, Karnataka, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"ramesh.kumar@infosys.com"}]

USER: "Priya Singh, born on 15/05/1990, works as a software engineer in Pune, Maharashtra, India. Her phone number is +91 (987) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Priya Singh"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"15/05/1990"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Pune, Maharashtra, India"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"}]

USER: "Visit our website at www.example.in and contact us at contact@example.in. Our company, ABC India Pvt. Ltd., is located in Mumbai City, Maharashtra."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.example.in"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@example.in"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC India Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai City, Maharashtra"}]

USER: "Aadhar number of Vinay Sharma is 1234 5678 9012."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Vinay Sharma"},{"entity":"ID","text":"1234 5678 9012"}]

USER: "The IP address 192.168.0.1 belongs to the local network."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.0.1"}]

USER: "Sita Devi, a resident of Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India, turned 60 on 01/12/1963."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sita Devi"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"01/12/1963"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India"}]

USER: "Rajesh Kumar, CEO of XYZ Ltd., lives at 789 River Road, Jaipur, Rajasthan, India. His email is rajesh@xyzltd.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Kumar"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"CEO"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"789 River Road, Jaipur, Rajasthan, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"rajesh@xyzltd.in"}]

USER: "Call our customer support at +91 (123) 456-7890 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (123) 456-7890"}]

USER: "The official website of the Indian government is www.india.gov.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.india.gov.in"}]

USER: "Harish Patel, an engineer at ABC Infotech Pvt. Ltd., lives at 567 Lake View Apartments, Hyderabad, Telangana, India. Contact him at harish@abcinfotech.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Harish Patel"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Infotech Pvt. Ltd."},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"567 Lake View Apartments, Hyderabad, Telangana, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"harish@abcinfotech.in"}]

USER: "Amit Sharma, residing at 123 Raj Nagar, Delhi, India, is 35 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Amit Sharma"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Raj Nagar, Delhi, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"}]

USER: "The account number of Preeti Verma is 5678901234."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Preeti Verma"},{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"5678901234"}]

USER: "Rajesh Gupta, a manager at ABC Bank, lives in Kolkata, West Bengal, India. You can reach him at rajesh@abcbank.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajesh Gupta"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"ABC Bank"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"Kolkata, West Bengal, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"rajesh@abcbank.in"}]

USER: "The IP address 203.0.113.1 is assigned to the server."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"203.0.113.1"}]

USER: "For job inquiries, visit our careers page at www.examplecareers.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.examplecareers.in"}]

USER: "Mr. Arvind Kumar, a resident of Mumbai, Maharashtra, India, celebrated his 50th birthday on 08/25/1973."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Mr. Arvind Kumar"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"08/25/1973"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"}]

USER: "The customer support hotline is +91 (987) 654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-3210"}]

USER: "The official government email is info@gov.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@gov.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website for more information: www.exampleproducts.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.exampleproducts.co.in"}]

USER: "Sheela Devi, a teacher in Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India, is 45 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sheela Devi"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"teacher"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"45 years old"}]

USER: "The account number of Sunil Kumar is 9876543210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sunil Kumar"},{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"9876543210"}]

USER: "Contact support at +91 (987) 654-9876 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (987) 654-9876"}]

USER: "The website www.exampleindia.com has all the details you need."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.exampleindia.com"}]

USER: "Rita Sharma, a project manager at XYZ Solutions, lives at 234 Park Street, Bangalore, Karnataka, India. Her email is rita@xyzsolutions.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rita Sharma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"XYZ Solutions"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"234 Park Street, Bangalore, Karnataka, India"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"rita@xyzsolutions.in"}]

USER: "The IP address 172.16.0.1 is used for internal communication."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"172.16.0.1"}]

USER: "For career opportunities, visit www.examplecareers.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.examplecareers.co.in"}]

USER: "Dr. Anjali Desai, a physician in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India, is 42 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Dr. Anjali Desai"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"physician"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"42 years old"}]

USER: "The customer support hotline is +91 (789) 456-1230."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 456-1230"}]

USER: "The official government email is contact@gov.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"contact@gov.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website for more information: www.exampleproducts.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.exampleproducts.in"}]

USER: "Vikram Singh, a lawyer in New Delhi, India, is 37 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Vikram Singh"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"lawyer"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"37 years old"}]

USER: "The account number of Rekha Sharma is 6543210987."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rekha Sharma"},{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"6543210987"}]

USER: "Contact support at +91 (789) 123-4567 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-4567"}]

USER: "The website www.exampleindia.in has all the details you need."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.exampleindia.in"}]

USER: "Alok Gupta, an architect in Hyderabad, Telangana, India, is 40 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Alok Gupta"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"architect"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Hyderabad, Telangana, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"40 years old"}]

USER: "The IP address 192.168.1.1 is used for the local network."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"192.168.1.1"}]

USER: "For career opportunities, visit www.examplecareers.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.examplecareers.in"}]

USER: "Dr. Sneha Patel, a dentist in Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India, is 35 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Dr. Sneha Patel"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"dentist"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"35 years old"}]

USER: "The customer support hotline is +91 (789) 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 987-6543"}]

USER: "The official government email is info@govt.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@govt.in"}]

USER: "Visit our website for more information: www.exampleproducts.co.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.exampleproducts.co.in"}]

USER: "Rajat Sharma, a journalist in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India, is 30 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Rajat Sharma"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"journalist"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Mumbai, Maharashtra, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"30 years old"}]

USER: "The account number of Meena Verma is 8765432109."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Meena Verma"},{"entity":"ACCOUNT_NUMBER","text":"8765432109"}]

USER: "Contact support at +91 (789) 654-3210 for assistance."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 654-3210"}]

USER: "The website www.exampleindia.com has all the details you need."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.exampleindia.com"}]

USER: "Suresh Kumar, a professor in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India, is 50 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Suresh Kumar"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"professor"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"50 years old"}]

USER: "The IP address 10.0.0.1 is used for internal communication."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"IP_ADDRESS","text":"10.0.0.1"}]

USER: "For career opportunities, visit www.examplecareers.in."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.examplecareers.in"}]

USER: "Dr. Nisha Gupta, a psychiatrist in New Delhi, India, is 38 years old."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Dr. Nisha Gupta"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"psychiatrist"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"New Delhi, India"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"38 years old"}]

USER: "The customer support hotline is +91 (789) 123-9876."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+91 (789) 123-9876"}]

USER: "Peter Schmidt, a software engineer at EuropeTech Ltd, lives at 45 Elm Street, Berlin, Germany. You can reach him at +49 (30) 123-4567 or peter@email.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Peter Schmidt"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuropeTech Ltd"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"45 Elm Street, Berlin, Germany"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+49 (30) 123-4567"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"peter@email.com"}]

USER: "Maria Rossi is an architect working for EuroDesigns in Milan, Italy. She was born on 05/15/1980 and can be contacted at +39 (02) 987-6543 or maria@email.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Maria Rossi"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"architect"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroDesigns"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Milan, Italy"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"05/15/1980"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+39 (02) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"maria@email.com"}]

USER: "Visit our European headquarters at 123 Avenue des Champs-lyses, Paris, France. Contact us at info@eurocorp.eu or call +33 (1) 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Avenue des Champs-lyses, Paris, France"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@eurocorp.eu"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+33 (1) 8765-4321"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Paris, France"}]

USER: "Anna Mller, a lawyer, works for EuroLegal in Vienna, Austria. You can email her at anna@email.at or call +43 (1) 7654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Anna Mller"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"lawyer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroLegal"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Vienna, Austria"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"anna@email.at"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+43 (1) 7654-3210"}]

USER: "I live at 78 King's Road, London, United Kingdom. Please send correspondence to my email, john@email.uk."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"78 King's Road, London, United Kingdom"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"john@email.uk"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"London, United Kingdom"}]

USER: "EuroBank, located at 56 Rue de la Banque, Brussels, Belgium, can be reached at +32 (2) 345-6789 or info@eurobank.be."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroBank"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"56 Rue de la Banque, Brussels, Belgium"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+32 (2) 345-6789"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@eurobank.be"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Brussels, Belgium"}]

USER: "Sophia Schneider, an engineer, resides at 22 Alpenstrasse, Zurich, Switzerland. You can contact her at +41 (44) 567-8901 or sophia@email.ch."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sophia Schneider"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"engineer"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"22 Alpenstrasse, Zurich, Switzerland"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+41 (44) 567-8901"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sophia@email.ch"}]

USER: "If you have any questions, visit our website at www.europroducts.eu or send us an email at info@europroducts.eu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.europroducts.eu"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@europroducts.eu"}]

USER: "Michael Jensen is a project manager at EuroTech in Munich, Germany. He can be reached at +49 (89) 4321-5678 or michael@email.de."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Michael Jensen"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroTech"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Munich, Germany"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+49 (89) 4321-5678"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"michael@email.de"}]

USER: "Our European office is located at 33 Gran Va, Madrid, Spain. For inquiries, please email us at europe@company.es."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"33 Gran Va, Madrid, Spain"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"europe@company.es"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Madrid, Spain"}]

USER: "Emma Smith, a marketing manager at EuroMedia, resides at 7 Strandvgen, Stockholm, Sweden. Contact her at +46 (8) 7654-3210 or emma@email.se."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Emma Smith"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"marketing manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroMedia"},{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"7 Strandvgen, Stockholm, Sweden"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+46 (8) 7654-3210"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"emma@email.se"}]

USER: "Visit our European data center at 123 Data Street, Amsterdam, Netherlands. Contact us at support@eurodata.nl."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"123 Data Street, Amsterdam, Netherlands"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@eurodata.nl"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Amsterdam, Netherlands"}]

USER: "Maxim Petrov is a software developer at EuroSoft in Moscow, Russia. You can email him at maxim@email.ru or call +7 (495) 123-4567."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Maxim Petrov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroSoft"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Moscow, Russia"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+7 (495) 123-4567"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"maxim@email.ru"}]

USER: "For the latest updates, visit our European news portal at www.euronews.eu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.euronews.eu"}]

USER: "Sophie Dubois, a journalist, works for EuroPress in Paris, France. She was born on 02/10/1992 and can be contacted at +33 (1) 9876-5432 or sophie@email.fr."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sophie Dubois"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"journalist"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroPress"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Paris, France"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"02/10/1992"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+33 (1) 9876-5432"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sophie@email.fr"}]

USER: "Our European factory is located at 44 Industriestrae, Frankfurt, Germany. For inquiries, please email us at info@eurofactory.de."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"44 Industriestrae, Frankfurt, Germany"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@eurofactory.de"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Frankfurt, Germany"}]

USER: "Andrea Bianchi is a sales manager at EuroTrade in Rome, Italy. You can email her at andrea@email.it or call +39 (06) 6543-2109."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Andrea Bianchi"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"sales manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroTrade"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Rome, Italy"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+39 (06) 6543-2109"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"andrea@email.it"}]

USER: "For the best European cuisine, visit our restaurant at 99 Rue de la Cuisine, Lyon, France. Reservations can be made at reservations@eurorestaurant.fr."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"99 Rue de la Cuisine, Lyon, France"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"reservations@eurorestaurant.fr"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Lyon, France"}]

USER: "Hans Mller, a professor, teaches at EuroUniversity in Berlin, Germany. You can reach him at +49 (30) 2345-6789 or hans@email.de."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Hans Mller"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"professor"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroUniversity"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Berlin, Germany"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+49 (30) 2345-6789"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"hans@email.de"}]

USER: "For travel bookings within Europe, visit www.eurotravel.com or contact us at bookings@eurotravel.com."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurotravel.com"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"bookings@eurotravel.com"}]

USER: "Sophia Fischer is a financial analyst at EuroFinance in Zurich, Switzerland. You can email her at sophia@email.ch or call +41 (44) 5678-9012."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sophia Fischer"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"financial analyst"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroFinance"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Zurich, Switzerland"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+41 (44) 5678-9012"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sophia@email.ch"}]

USER: "For EuroTech support, visit our European help center at 55 Supportstrae, Vienna, Austria. Contact us at support@eurotech.at."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"55 Supportstrae, Vienna, Austria"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@eurotech.at"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Vienna, Austria"}]

USER: "Pavel Ivanov is a software engineer at EuroSoft in Moscow, Russia. You can email him at pavel@email.ru or call +7 (495) 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Pavel Ivanov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software engineer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroSoft"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Moscow, Russia"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+7 (495) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"pavel@email.ru"}]

USER: "For the latest European fashion trends, visit our website at www.eurofashion.eu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurofashion.eu"}]

USER: "Lukas Kov is a project manager at EuroProjects in Prague, Czech Republic. You can email him at lukas@email.cz or call +420 123-456-789."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Lukas Kov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroProjects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Prague, Czech Republic"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+420 123-456-789"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"lukas@email.cz"}]

USER: "Our European warehouse is located at 66 Lagerstrae, Budapest, Hungary. For inquiries, please email us at info@eurowarehouse.hu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"66 Lagerstrae, Budapest, Hungary"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@eurowarehouse.hu"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Budapest, Hungary"}]

USER: "Olga Petrova is a marketing manager at EuroMedia in Kyiv, Ukraine. You can email her at olga@email.ua or call +380 44 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Olga Petrova"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"marketing manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroMedia"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kyiv, Ukraine"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+380 44 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"olga@email.ua"}]

USER: "Explore the beauty of Europe with EuroTours. Visit our website at www.eurotours.com for travel packages."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurotours.com"}]

USER: "Elena Romano, a journalist, reports for EuroNews in Madrid, Spain. She was born on 12/05/1987 and can be contacted at +34 91 7654-3210 or elena@email.es."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Elena Romano"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"journalist"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroNews"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Madrid, Spain"},{"entity":"AGE","text":"12/05/1987"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+34 91 7654-3210"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"elena@email.es"}]

USER: "Our European manufacturing plant is located at 77 Fabrikstrae, Warsaw, Poland. For inquiries, please email us at info@europlant.pl."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"77 Fabrikstrae, Warsaw, Poland"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@europlant.pl"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Warsaw, Poland"}]

USER: "Andreas Wagner is a sales manager at EuroSales in Vienna, Austria. You can email him at andreas@email.at or call +43 (1) 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Andreas Wagner"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"sales manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroSales"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Vienna, Austria"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+43 (1) 8765-4321"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"andreas@email.at"}]

USER: "For EuroCuisine recipes, visit our website at www.eurocuisine.eu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurocuisine.eu"}]

USER: "Sofia Papadopoulos is a financial analyst at EuroFinance in Athens, Greece. You can email her at sofia@email.gr or call +30 21 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sofia Papadopoulos"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"financial analyst"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroFinance"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Athens, Greece"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+30 21 8765-4321"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sofia@email.gr"}]

USER: "For EuroTech product support, visit our European help center at 88 Supportstrae, Berlin, Germany. Contact us at support@eurotech.de."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"88 Supportstrae, Berlin, Germany"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@eurotech.de"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Berlin, Germany"}]

USER: "Ivan Kuznetsov is a software developer at EuroSoft in St. Petersburg, Russia. You can email him at ivan@email.ru or call +7 (812) 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ivan Kuznetsov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroSoft"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"St. Petersburg, Russia"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+7 (812) 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"ivan@email.ru"}]

USER: "For the latest European tech news, visit our website at www.eurotechnews.eu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurotechnews.eu"}]

USER: "Nina Kovov is a project manager at EuroProjects in Bratislava, Slovakia. You can email her at nina@email.sk or call +421 2 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Nina Kovov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroProjects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Bratislava, Slovakia"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+421 2 8765-4321"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"nina@email.sk"}]

USER: "Our European distribution center is located at 99 Vertriebstrae, Prague, Czech Republic. For inquiries, please email us at info@eurodistrib.cz."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"99 Vertriebstrae, Prague, Czech Republic"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@eurodistrib.cz"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Prague, Czech Republic"}]

USER: "Maria Ivanova is a marketing manager at EuroMedia in Kiev, Ukraine. You can email her at maria@email.ua or call +380 44 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Maria Ivanova"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"marketing manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroMedia"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Kiev, Ukraine"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+380 44 8765-4321"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"maria@email.ua"}]

USER: "Explore Europe's finest wines with EuroWines. Visit our website at www.eurowines.eu for wine selections."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurowines.eu"}]

USER: "Andreas Schmidt is a professor at EuroUniversity in Munich, Germany. You can email him at andreas@email.de or call +49 (89) 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Andreas Schmidt"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"professor"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroUniversity"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Munich, Germany"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+49 (89) 8765-4321"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"andreas@email.de"}]

USER: "For EuroFood recipes, visit our website at www.eurofoodrecipes.eu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurofoodrecipes.eu"}]

USER: "Sophie Dupont is a financial analyst at EuroFinance in Paris, France. You can email her at sophie@email.fr or call +33 (1) 7654-3210."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Sophie Dupont"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"financial analyst"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroFinance"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Paris, France"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+33 (1) 7654-3210"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"sophie@email.fr"}]

USER: "For EuroTech product support, visit our European help center at 77 Supportstrae, Vienna, Austria. Contact us at support@eurotech.at."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"77 Supportstrae, Vienna, Austria"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"support@eurotech.at"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Vienna, Austria"}]

USER: "Ivan Petrov is a software developer at EuroSoft in Sofia, Bulgaria. You can email him at ivan@email.bg or call +359 2 987-6543."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Ivan Petrov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"software developer"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroSoft"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Sofia, Bulgaria"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+359 2 987-6543"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"ivan@email.bg"}]

USER: "For the latest European travel tips, visit our website at www.eurotraveltips.eu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"URL","text":"www.eurotraveltips.eu"}]

USER: "Eva Novkov is a project manager at EuroProjects in Prague, Czech Republic. You can email her at eva@email.cz or call +420 2 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Eva Novkov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"project manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroProjects"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Prague, Czech Republic"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+420 2 8765-4321"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"eva@email.cz"}]

USER: "Our European distribution center is located at 88 Vertriebstrae, Budapest, Hungary. For inquiries, please email us at info@eurodistrib.hu."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"ADDRESS","text":"88 Vertriebstrae, Budapest, Hungary"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"info@eurodistrib.hu"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Budapest, Hungary"}]

USER: "Alexei Ivanov is a marketing manager at EuroMedia in Moscow, Russia. You can email him at alexei@email.ru or call +7 (495) 8765-4321."
ASSISTANT: [{"entity":"PERSON","text":"Alexei Ivanov"},{"entity":"JOB_TITLE","text":"marketing manager"},{"entity":"COMPANY","text":"EuroMedia"},{"entity":"LOCATION","text":"Moscow, Russia"},{"entity":"PHONE","text":"+7 (495) 8765-4321"},{"entity":"EMAIL","text":"alexei@email.ru"}]
